{
    "id": "297f9f5d59bb4e1687dfc0633e2f928b",
    "title": "Make, Take Or Leave",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Can I ………………… a suggestion?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "take",
                "leave",
                "make"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "24af99e3094f49d0a7853c35da6e9995"
        },
        {
            "question": "One must not …………………… more than one gives.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "leave",
                "make",
                "take"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e5cc361dc4974af491bcc001296e6dab"
        },
        {
            "question": "Please …………………… a look at this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "take",
                "make",
                "leave"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a9799cff37744553b3ecf6e0681cca78"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can I ……………………… a message?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "take",
                "leave",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "638df3a7c01645b68db3064765439b32"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t …………………… an exception in your case.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "make",
                "take",
                "leave"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8882f6ee555b49789254a412ada82404"
        },
        {
            "question": "My brother likes to ………………….. photos.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "take",
                "leave",
                "make"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ef6c3d8784404b1bba174b7bae5d5546"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have …………………. all arrangements for the party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "taken",
                "left",
                "made"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "08ee0d17038d44239ede19801462179b"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is old enough to ………………… her own bed now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "take",
                "make",
                "leave"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "556384d64bc34968bf3fcceb661f1557"
        },
        {
            "question": "If you are tired why don’t you ………………….. a rest?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "take",
                "make",
                "leave"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a06f1323e13b47098853868584c58faa"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………… a deep breath.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "took",
                "made",
                "left"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7f989e3ae8304de0b60dbddbe3fc9b48"
        }
    ]
}